

CAIO GOMES BRAGA

Full-stack developer

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

Self-taught freelance programmer for 4 years with great teamwork skills. In 2021 I started to study computer science at the Federal University of Viçosa with the objective of expanding and perfecting my skills. I have technical education in computers and some work experience. I am currently looking for a job with more stability. My professional goal is to work as a junior developer. I have the ability to develop web and mobile systems.

PRAÇA ISIDORO BINDA, 110, VILA NOVA



caiotagb@gmail.com



HTTPS://PROGRAMADOR-DE-QUINTAL.WEBNODE.COM/PO RTFOLIO/



55 + (27) 98886-0342



I HAVE MOBILITY TO CHANGE CITY / STATE / COUNTRY



LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Portuguese Native
- Spanish intermediary

EDUCATION

SKILLS

EXPERTISE

Computer Technician for the Internet Federal Institution of Espirito Santo, Colatina, Concluded, 2017-2020

Bachelor in Computer Science Universidade Federal de Viçosa, In progress. 2021

React.js and react native courses - UDEMY, Completed, 2018-2019

NODEJS, REACT, REACT NATIVE, PROGRESSIVE WEB APPS, GRAPHQL, VUEJS, NEXTJS, SQL, REST, MONGODB, HTML5, ANGULAR, JAVASCRIPT, CSS, PYTHON, GIT, UNIX, WINDOWS, C, C++, C SHARP, DOCKER, WORDPRESS WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT

WEBSITE MAINTENANCE

REMOTE API INTEGRATION

REPORT WRITING

UX DESIGN

EXPERIENCE

E-COMMERCE DEVELOPER

- Learning about the use of wordpress
- Development of communication with producers and directors for job requirements.
- Development of communicative skills, teamwork and design

FREELANCER.

COLATINA-ES

04/2017-05/2017

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

- During this period, websites were developed with react.js and other technologies for different customers.
- Use of social networks to contact and get customers among other sites and referrals from people who liked the service
- Skills development for website maintenance and code versioning
- Skill development for reading third-party systems documentation and Skill for independent learning.

FREELANCER

COLATINA-ES

06/2017-PRESENTE

APP DEVELOPER

- During this period, they were developed with react-native and other technologies for varied clients and personal projects.
- Use of social networks to contact and get customers among other sites and referrals from people who liked the service
- Developing skills for maintaining code sites and creating a favorable development environment
- Skill development for reading third-party systems documentation and Skill for independent learning.

FREELANCER

COLATINA-ES

08/2017-PRESENTE